MARTA RANDAZZO

@ randazzomarta@icloud.com

**** +39 351 207 7159

04011 Aprilia

♀ Latium, Italy

Hi! I'm Marta, 24 years old front end developer from Rome, Italy. I can easily balance my time with a job and university and I love having multiple sources of stimuli, since I'm very curious about anything regarding the tech field. I'm a videogamer and a perfectionist, I never start a game if I don't 100/100 complete it, if you know what I mean.

EXPERIENCE

Job Experience

DEAS S.p.A. - Difesa E Analisi Sistemi

October 2023 - Present

Rome / Hybrid

This experience made me improve - a lot - my React competences since I worked on various applications with different teams. I also learned how to manage my time when a lot of priorities occur.

- Started as a Junior Software Developer, mainly regarding the front end development of various products. I was mainly involved in Angular projects.
- Worked following the agile method, with daily scrums and sprint planning and retrospectives. Used softwares like Teams, DBeaver, Docker Desktop and GitLab to manage my tasks.
- I gained proficiency in working with APIs and verifying all the data I needed through DBeaver or through Swagger UI. I was mainly involved in Angular projects.
- I also worked on the maintenance of the Wordpress site of my company and drew up the documentation for a project I was involved in.

Job Experience

Coderblock

🗎 July 2022 - October 2023

Palermo / Hybrid

This experience helped me grow a lot since I gained confidence as a developer and grew my love for the tech field.

- Started my journey as a Web Designer (I worked as a graphic designer and as a frontend developer).
- Worked following the agile method. Used softwares like Slack, Trello, Miro and GitHub Projects to optimize my work experience inside the office.
- I mainly used Angular and started learning React with Node.JS, learned about APIs and other CSS frameworks such as Tailwind and Sass as a CSS extension.
- Optimization for HUD designs (I worked with Unity developers for the HUD of our environment), Photoshop settings for professional print (for promotional gadgets and events) and new designs in Illustrator, Photoshop and Sketch for the landings I've been developing in Angular.
- You can find some of my web development projects here, here and here.

STRENGTHS

Eye for detail Curious Learner
Fast learner Perfectionist

Clean code Clear documentation

Efficient task management



LANGUAGES

Italian - C2 English - B2

Spanish - A1

EDUCATION

BSc, Computer Science Università di Roma - Sapienza

di October 2022 - Ongoing

High School, Humanities Liceo Classico Statale "Vittorio Emanuele II", Palermo

₩ Jul 2019

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

The Odin Project Course

March 2024 - May 2024

• Developing web apps using Ruby.

The complete Ruby on Rails Developer Course

May 2024 - Present

• Here's the course link

PROJECTS

DreamTeam

- Projecting a web application for school notes sharing using Agile Methodology
- Gained proficiency in using Eclipse for Java Enterprise Edition, MySQL Workbench and Apache Tomcat for the server.
- Developed the whole front end part of the project using Bootstrap as my CSS framework.

JBomberman

- 🛗 June 2023 January 2024
- Remote working
- Creating a Java version of the old Bomberman game.
- Currently using Eclipse for my java project.
- Working with Swing and JavaFX, using design patterns such as MVC for components' responsibilities management.

WASAPhoto

- May 2024 ongoing
- **♀** Remote working
- Creating a web app for photo sharing.
- Currently using GO for the backend and Vue.js for the frontend.
- Working with Docker and Kubernetes.

Graphic Design Projects

- September 2019 Present
- **♀** Fiverr/Social Media
- 5+ years experience with Adobe Photoshop.
- Designs for an esport italian competitive team.
- Art commissions for local shops and university radio podcasts.
- Social media content for IG pages.
- Most of my art is on my Behance profile: Behance Portfolio

PRIVACY

• I give consent to process my data with the purpose of the recruitment process, in accordance to the Regulation of the European Parliament 679/2016, regarding the protection of natural persons and free movement of such data